<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on Life Tank</title>
        <link>https://lifetank.life/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on Life Tank</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 22:21:48 -0600</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://lifetank.life/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>whoami</title>
            <link>https://lifetank.life/posts/whoami_002/</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 22:21:48 -0600</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://lifetank.life/posts/whoami_002/</guid>
            <description>My name is Nathan Curtis. For some time I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to take the time to write down thoughts and ideas.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>My name is Nathan Curtis. For some time I&rsquo;ve wanted to take the time to write down thoughts and ideas. More than those general things, I&rsquo;ve wanted to talk about what I&rsquo;ve been researching and reading the past few years. My brother finally convinvced me to help him spin up a site that can hold all of those things. I hope to explore many things throughout the existence of this site, however long or short that is. Many things in life can happen that stifles productivity, maintaining a schedule, and writing well crafted articles. My goal is to be diligent about those things and to always strive for the most un-biased writings.</p>
<p>Here&rsquo;s a list of topics that I want to cover:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Early Civilizations</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Future Civilizations</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Psychadelics</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Sensemaking</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Game B</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Economics</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Decentralization</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Programming / Tech</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>AI</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>I Hope you find what you are looking for.</p>
<p><em>Nathan</em></p>
<p><em>find me @</em><a href="https://twitter.com/nathan_jcurtis">nathan_jcurtis</a></p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Thoughts on Death Stranding</title>
            <link>https://lifetank.life/posts/thoughts-on-death-stranding/</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 22:18:50 -0500</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://lifetank.life/posts/thoughts-on-death-stranding/</guid>
            <description>Story Synopsis: The game is set in the United States following a cataclysmic event which caused destructive creatures to begin roaming the Earth.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Story Synopsis:
The game is set in the United States following a cataclysmic event which caused destructive creatures to begin roaming the Earth. Players control Sam Porter Bridges (Norman Reedus), a courier tasked with delivering supplies to isolated colonies and reconnecting them via a wireless communications network.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>test the comments</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>this is a list</li>
<li>another point</li>
</ul>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
