<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Eureka Demo</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Eureka Demo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wangchucheng.com/&#34;&gt;C. Wang&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ruiqima.com/&#34;&gt;R. Ma&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 14:41:06 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Useful Links for Anyone That Uses the Internet</title>
      <link>/posts/useful-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 14:41:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/useful-links/</guid>
      <description>Favorites  archive.org - The Internet Archive furturetimeline.net futureme.org ninite.com 10minutemail.com pointerpointer.com   Other favorites  Utility Consumers Productivity Learning    It&amp;rsquo;s the day after Thanksgiving, you&amp;rsquo;re sitting around and wondering &amp;ldquo;why have I looked at the same links on Reddit five times already?&amp;rdquo;. Or maybe you just need to look busy to avoid contact with those other humans in your house. You&amp;rsquo;re in luck, because here is a collection of some interesting sites that may help you be (or look) productive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>whoami_kenneth</title>
      <link>/posts/whoami_kenneth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 16:50:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/whoami_kenneth/</guid>
      <description>My name is Kenneth. This site came about because I had so many thoughts in my head and nowhere to put them. This is a place where I will dump my ideas about philosophy, entertainment, media, technology, and general thoughts on living in this world. Not everything will be written to perfection. This will be a learning experience, and a therapeutic one. I hope whoever reads this enjoys my perspective and experience in this life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019|2020 Booklist</title>
      <link>/posts/booklist_003/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 13:53:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/booklist_003/</guid>
      <description>In the middle of 2019 I really started to make an effort to continuously be reading a book. As soon as I finished one, I should start another. The subject didn&amp;rsquo;t matter and neither did the continuation of a certain topic that I was interested in at the time. While timing did have an impact depending on what books were coming out at the time, I still made an effort to keep my choice to read a certain book up to chance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>whoami</title>
      <link>/posts/whoami_002/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 22:21:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/whoami_002/</guid>
      <description>For some time I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to take the time to write down thoughts and ideas. More than those general things, I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to talk about what I&amp;rsquo;ve been researching and reading the past few years. My brother finally convinvced me to help him spin up a site that can hold all of those things. I hope to explore many things throughout the existence of this site, however long or short that is. Many things in life can happen that stifles productivity, maintaining a schedule, and writing well crafted articles.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
